I just wanted somebody to believe me.
My Amityville Horror is a documentary, horror film directed by Eric Walter.
For the first time in 35 years, Daniel Lutz recounts his version of the
infamous Amityville haunting that terrified his family in 1975.
George and Kathleen Lutz's story went on to inspire a best-selling novel and the
subsequent films have continued to fascinate audiences today.
This documentary reveals the horror behind growing up as part of a world-famous haunting and while
Daniel's facts may be others' fiction, the psychological scars he carries are indisputable.
Documentary filmmaker Eric Walter has combined years of independent research into the Amityville case along with the perspectives
of past investigative reporters and eyewitnesses, giving way to the most personal testimony of the subject to date.
Himself, played by Daniel Lutz.
Herself, played by Susan Bartell.
Herself, played by Laura DiDio.
Himself, played by Marvin Scott.
The Amityville haunting is a modern folk story based
on the true crimes of Ronald DeFeo Jr.
On November 13, 1974, DeFeo shot and killed six members of his family at 112
Ocean Avenue, Amityville, on the south shore of Long Island.
He was convicted of second-degree murder in November 1975.
In December 1975, George and Kathy Lutz and their
three children moved into the house.
After 28 days, the Lutzes left the house, claiming to have been
terrorized by paranormal phenomena while living there.
The house became the subject of numerous investigations by journalists,
skeptics, and paranormal researchers, including Ed and Lorraine Warren.
These events served as the historical basis for Jay Anson's 1977 novel The Amityville Horror, which was
followed by a number of sequels and was adapted into a film of the same name in 1979.
Since then, many films have been produced that draw explicitly, to a greater
or lesser extent, from these historical and literary sources.
As Amityville is a real town and the stories of DeFeo and the Lutzes are historical, there can be no
proprietary relationship to the underlying  elements associated with the Amityville haunting.
As a result of this, there has been no restriction on the exploitation of the story by film producers, which is the reason that
most of these films share no continuity, were produced by different companies, and tell widely varying stories.
The Amityville Horror film, released in the summer of 1979, was a major box office success, and went
on to become one of the most commercially successful independent films of all time.
A series of sequels were released throughout the 1980s and into the 1990s through various distributors; some
of the films received theatrical distribution, while others were direct-to-video releases.
In 2005, a re-imagining of the first film was released.
Beginning in 2011, there was a resurgence of low-budget direct-to-video
independent films based on or loosely inspired by the Amityville events.
In 2017, The Weinstein Company and Dimension Films distributed the first
theatrical Amityville film since the 2005 re-imagining.
Amityville: The Awakening, which was filmed in 2014, was released theatrically in
Ukraine on July 27, 2017, and in the United States on October 28, 2017.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.